Shea Odland

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- 780-910-9800
- sheaodland@gmail.com
- Edmonton / Alberta / Canada
- <u>LinkedIn</u>
- % Github
- www.sheaodland.com

ABOUT ME

Whether it's developing helpful software for a business or fixing drainage issues for a homeowner, I take pride in providing everyone a solution to their unique needs.

With over a decade of experience in the landscaping industry and an education in Computer Science, my unique experience provides valuable perspective to employers and clients.

SKILLS

Scrum Framework,

Known Computer Languages include: Python, C, C#, Java, SQL, Dart, HTML, CSS;

Experienced in: Scum Agile Development, Flutter, Firebase, Unity, Relational Database Systems, NoSQL databases, Project Management, Leadership, Computer Drafting (AutoCAD, Dynascape, Sketchup), Design, Estimating, Budgeting, Inventory Management, Safety Management, Career Building, Recruiting, Equipment Operation

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

MacEwan University

Environmental Horticulture

Olds College 2009-2011

EXPERIENCE

Landscape Foreman

Terra Landscaping / Edmonton, AB / May 2016 – August 2017

- Managed the demands of both client and management
- Constructed indoor living walls
- Operated small and heavy equipment.

Landscape Manager

You Dream It We Build It / Sherwood Park, AB / April 2015 – May 2016

- Developed relationships with suppliers, clients, and potential business partners
- Managed the day-to-day operations
- Designed, bid, and constructed a variety of residential landscaping projects

Landscape Designer/Foreman

Three Seasons Landscaping Ltd. / Ardrossan, AB / April 2008 – August 2013

- Implemented budgeting and hr systems
- Consulted, estimated and managed construction
- Conducted on-site hazard assessments, equipment circle checks, and daily planning meetings